{
    "id": "a62fc88c36d1404abb902d827dd8f660",
    "title": "See, Look, Watch",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can you …………………………. anything over there?",
            "description": "We do not normally use the progressive forms of see when it means perceive with one’s eyes.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "watch",
                "seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘................................! We are going to crash.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "See",
                "Look",
                "Watch"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Can you repair the radio in a couple of hours?’ ‘Let me ………………………’",
            "description": "The expression let me see can mean let me find out.",
            "answers": [
                "look",
                "see",
                "watch"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ……………………….. much better since I changed my glasses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "watching",
                "looking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. your dad tomorrow.",
            "description": "When see means meet, progressive forms are possible.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "watching",
                "looking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. something moving behind the curtain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "watched",
                "looked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you ……………………….. at me like that?",
            "description": "To look at something or somebody is to pay attention.",
            "answers": [
                "looking",
                "seeing",
                "watching"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘…………………………. here.’",
            "description": "Before an object, we use look at.",
            "answers": [
                "Look",
                "Look at",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A ……………………….. pot never boils.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "seen",
                "looked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Police have been …………………………… him for a while.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "watching",
                "looking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. a great movie yesterday.",
            "description": "Watch and see are both used to talk about TV programs and films.",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "watched",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. if dinner is ready.",
            "description": "See can be used in the sense of find out. It is followed by if/whether.",
            "answers": [
                "See",
                "Watch",
                "Look"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}